

PAVEL ŠINDELÁŘ

CONTACT

- +420 722 042 944
- sindelar.pavel97@gmail.com
- Portfolio
- Linkedin

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE

University of Finance and Administration, a.s. Applied Informatics 2020 - 2024

STATE MATRICULATION EXAM

Private Secondary School and Primary School (1. KŠPA), Prague

18-20-M/01 Informatics 2016 - 2020

APPRENTICESHIP CERTIFICATE

Secondary Vocational School of Catering, Říčany s.r.o. 65-51-H/01 Chef - Waiter 2013 - 2016

SKILLS

Angular, RxJS, NGXS, Angular Material, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Tailwind Git, Docker

LANGUAGES

Czech - Native speaker English - B2

ABOUT ME

I am a web developer with more than two years of experience in Angular development. I focus on creating modern and user-friendly single-page applications (SPAs) that provide a seamless and efficient user experience. I enjoy learning new technologies, taking on challenges, and continuously improving my skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB AND MOBILE APP DEVELOPER BIRDROCK REI INC, SAN ANTONIO, TX

Angular and Ionic Developer

Developed SPA and PWA applications in Angular focused on real estate management, API integration, and UI optimization.

FOUR SEASONS HOTELS LIMITED

JULY 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

DECEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

IT Support Specialist

Managed user accounts using Windows Active Directory in a hotel environment, resolved technical issues via a ticketing system, and performed data backups.

ZOOT A.S.

MAY 2018 - NOVEMBER 2020

IT Support Specialist

Configured and maintained IoT devices, monitored networks, managed connected devices, and provided user support.

PROJECTS

WEB APPLICATION BIRDROCKRES

Real Estate Management Application

A web application designed for efficient management of rental properties. Built with Angular, featuring document management and photo organization functionalities.

MOBILE APPLICATION BIRDROCKRES

PWA for Real Estate Management

A supplement to the web application, developed in Ionic, providing seamless access from mobile devices.